Here, in the east, the equipment does not last long because of the fighting.
It often needs major repairs and new parts.
Masters of the 80th Brigade's repair company restore both damaged armored vehicles and weapons to life.
This is a section of the repair company.
What are your duties?
Restoration, repair of weapons equipment, which is on...
on the register of the military unit.
What is the most common range of tasks you perform here?
What kind of equipment?
Or all the equipment in general?
All the equipment. Various.
Starts with cars provided by volunteers, units, battalions.
He closes it all with tanks.
And what's the most difficult stage?
Weapons.
There is an experienced gunsmith in Remroth.
Vitaliy is proficient with various calibers, from pistols to large-caliber machine guns.
Neighboring brigades bring their weapons to us for repair.
They have no gunsmiths who have repaired weapons for anyone.
Here, in this case, it's an MG-42.
We collect MG-42s and MG-53s from Lihoslav, which we also have in our household.
We are currently under repair.
To cut out a complicated part for a foreign grenade launcher or weld the hull of a trophy APC, local craftsmen take on the most difficult orders from the front.
They say they can do anything.
Military television also made a small contribution to our victory.